Guide to the Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007
Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007
- Dean of Students Collection #37-1-1570
  - The Recognition of Student Organizations (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 2)
  - Agronomy Grad. School (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 2)
  - Plant Pathology Discussion Group (Graduate Group) (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 3)
  - Synapsis (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Singing Groups (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 5)
  - Savage Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 6)
  - Zoology Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 7)
  - W.S.G.A. (Woman's Student Government Association) (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1959 (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1960 (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1962 (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1958 (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 12)
  - Inter-class Council (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 13)
  - Alpha Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 14)
  - Algonquin Lodge (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 15)
  - Cayuga-Student Residence (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 16)
  - Shinguard (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 17)
  - Simga Delta Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 18)
  - Sigma Delta Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 19)
  - Simga Gamma Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 20)
  - Sigma Iota Zeta (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 21)
  - Socialist Study Group (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 22)
  - Society for Advancement of Management (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 23)
  - Sphinx Head (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 24)
  - Tau Beta Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 25)
  - Telluride Journal (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 26)
  - Two Year Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 27)
  - Undergraduate Chemical Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 28)
  - Undergraduate Committee on Secondary Schools (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 29)
  - Vegetable Crops Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 30)
  - Wesley Foundation (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 31)
  - Westminister Student Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 32)
  - Willard Straight Hall (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 33)
  - Women's Athletic Association (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 34)
  - YASNY (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 35)
  - Ye Hosts (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 36)
  - Young Democratic Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 37)
  - Young Friends Group (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 38)
  - Young Republican Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 39)
  - Aiesec (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 40)
  - Ag-Domecon Council (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 41)
  - Agricultural Economics Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 42)
  - All African Students Association (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 43)
  - Alpha Phi Omega (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 44)
  - Alpha Epsilon Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 45)
  - Alpha Epislon Kappa (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 46)
  - American Institution of Chemical Engineers (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 47)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 48)
  - Aquarius (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 49)
  - Arnold Air Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 50)
  - Atmos (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 51)
  - Alpha Alpha Gamma (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 52)
  - Bacamia (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 53)
  - Bahai Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 54)
  - Baptist Student Fellowship (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 55)
  - Beth-L'Amed (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 56)
  - Big Red Band (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 57)
  - Big Redmen (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 58)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillel (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 59)
  - Chi Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 60)
  - Chinese Students Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 61)
  - Christian Science Organization (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 62)
  - Committee for Sane Nuclear Policy of Cornell (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 63)
  - Congregational Student Association (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 64)
  - Cornell Amateur Radio Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 65)
  - Cornell Association of Teachers of Agriculture (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 66)
  - Cornell Cross Country Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 67)
  - Cornell English Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 68)
  - Cornell Filipino Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 69)
  - Cornell 4-H Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 70)
  - Cornell Jazz Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 71)
  - Cornell Red Cross Unit (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 72)
  - Cornell Skin Divers Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 73)
  - American Youth for Democracy (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 74)
  - Kappa Delta Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 75)
  - NAACP (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 76)
  - Varsity Managers Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 4, Folder 77)
  - Agromony Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 2)
  - Arts College Council, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 2)
  - Cayuga Waiters, 1958-1959 (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 3)
  - Cooperatives, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Brigade, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Business and Public Admin. Association, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Chess Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Committee against Segregation, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Conservation Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Crew Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Cricket Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Dairy Science Association, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Dance Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Debate Association, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Deskbook, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Dramatic Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Engineer, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Fencing Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Folk Dancers, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Folk Song Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Forum, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Graduate School of Business and Public Admin. Management, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Grange, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Gymnastics Association, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Hotel Association, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 27)
  - Cornell India Association, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Jazz Society, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Law Quarterly, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Law Student Association, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Newman Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Pilots Club, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Society of Engineering Physics, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Student Assembly, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 35)
  - Cornell University Concert Band, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 36)
  - Cornellian, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 37)
  - Gamma Alpha (Grad Scientific Frat), 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 38)
  - Mens Living Units, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 39)
  - Omega Tau Sigma, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 40)
  - Telluride, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 41)
  - Von Gramm Hall, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 42)
  - Watermargin, Inc., 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 43)
  - Young Israel Chapter, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 44)
  - Budget Directors File, 1962-1963 (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 45)
  - Centennial, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 46)
  - Finance Commission - Reports, Minutes, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 47)
  - Finance Commission, 1963 (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 48)
  - Finance Commission, 1964-1965 (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 49)
  - Report of the Committee on the Reorganization of Student Gov., 1959 (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 50)
  - Review and Recommendations Commission Report, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 51)
  - SCARB (Scheduling Coordination and Acitivites Review Board), 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 52)
  - Speeches - President Friedman, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 53)
  - Stencils I, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 54)
  - Stencils II, 1950's (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 55)
  - Student Government Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 37-1-1570 - 5, Folder 56)
  - Finance Commission - Report and Recommendations of Student Government and Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 2)
  - Finance Commission - Report and Recommendations of Student Government and Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 2)
  - Finance Commission of Student Government and Budget, 1964-1965 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 3)
  - Finance Commission - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 3a)
  - Finance Commission - Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 4)
  - Finance Commission of Student Government - Minutes, Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 5)
  - Finance Commission of Students Government - Minutes, Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 6)
  - Finance Commission Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 7)
  - Finance Commission - Budget Report and Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University Senate, 1970-1971 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University Senate, 1970-1971 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University Senate, 1970-1971 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 11)
  - Afro-American Society, 1968-1970 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 12)
  - Agronomy Club, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 13)
  - Archery Club, 1970 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 14)
  - Empty (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Draft Info Services, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Engineer, 1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 17)
  - Dance Club, 1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 18)
  - Debate Association, 1969-1970 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 19)
  - Dialogue Magazine, 1968 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 20)
  - Gay Lib Front (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 21)
  - Icans (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 22)
  - International Committee, 1970 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 23)
  - N.O.W., 1970 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 24)
  - Public Affairs Intern Program, 1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 25)
  - Round-Up Club, 1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 26)
  - Table Tennis (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 27)
  - Trojan Horse, 1968 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 28)
  - Political Funding, 1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 29)
  - Vocations for Social Change, 1970 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 30)
  - Waterpolo Club, 1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 31)
  - Finance Commission of Student Activities, 1971-1972 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 32)
  - Registration Forms, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 33)
  - Registration Forms, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 35)
  - Graduate Funding Commission, 1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 36)
  - Office of the Dean of Students - Minutes, Memos, 1970's (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 37)
  - Senate - Minutes of Meetings, 1976 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 38)
  - Ambassadors, 1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 39)
  - Black Activities Council, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 40)
  - Black Law Caucus, 1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 41)
  - Black Radio Ithaca, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 42)
  - Black View, 1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 43)
  - Blue Bus People, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 44)
  - Committee on Academic Responsibility, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 45)
  - Committee to Investigate Student Bargaining in Tuition, 1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 46)
  - Committee to Rape the Loch Ness Monster, 1972 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 47)
  - Community Service Education Student's Organization, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 48)
  - Concerned Students for Representative Gov., 1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 49)
  - Ethiopian Student's Group, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 50)
  - Friends of Human Ecology, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 51)
  - Friends of Human Ecology, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 51)
  - Garden Club, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 52)
  - Independent Radical Students, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 53)
  - Iranian Club, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 54)
  - Ithaca Call, 1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 55)
  - Ithaca Tenants Union (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 56)
  - Ivy League Monopoly Ass., 1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 57)
  - Jordani, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 58)
  - Korean Student's Association, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 59)
  - Kuumba Repertory Theatre (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 60)
  - Latin American Student Association, 1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 61)
  - Lubavitch Youth Organization, 1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 62)
  - Movement against Cutbacks, 1976 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 63)
  - Movement for a New Congress, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 64)
  - Muslim Association (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 65)
  - N.A.J., 1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 66)
  - Natural Foods Club, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 67)
  - New Writer, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 68)
  - No Suit Swimmers, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 69)
  - Octagon, 1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 70)
  - Open House, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 71)
  - Pakistan - Cornell Association, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 72)
  - Pep Squad, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 73)
  - Pi Mu Epsilon (Math), 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 74)
  - Pi Sigma Epsilon, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 75)
  - Polish Cultural Association, 1975-1976 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 76)
  - Radicals for Capitalism, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 78)
  - Rest of News, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 79)
  - Revolutionary Student Brigade, 1975-1976 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 80)
  - Senior Class Council, 1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 81)
  - Sex Education Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 82)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 83)
  - Spartacus Youth League, 1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 84)
  - Sport Parachute Club, 1972 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 85)
  - Steering Committee Interreligious International Ministry, 1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 86)
  - Tau Beta Pi, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 87)
  - Volunteer Student Security Patrol, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 88)
  - Cornell Widow, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 89)
  - Women and the Arts, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 90)
  - Young People's Socialist League, 1975-1976 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 91)
  - Youth Committee for Peace and Democracy in the Middle East, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 92)
  - Senate - Minutes, Standard Legislative Formats, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 93)
  - Senate - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 94)
  - Senate - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 37-1-1570 - 10, Folder 95)
  - Graduate Coordinating Council - Minutes, News Clippings, Constitution, Newsletters, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 2)
  - University Unions Executive Board, 1969-1972 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Coordinating Council - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Coordinating Council - Special Project Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 4)
  - Senate Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 5)
  - Information on Activities Submitted to be Organizations, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 6)
  - Special Project Requests, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Finance Commission Budget Requests, 1973-1974 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Coordinating Council Historical Information (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Coordinating Council, 1970-1971 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 10)
  - Budget Requests, 1972-1973 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 11)
  - Academic Support Peer Counselors, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 12)
  - Activities Festival Coordinating Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 13)
  - Agronomy Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 14)
  - AGPAC, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 15)
  - Alpha Epsilon Delta, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 16)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 17)
  - Amateur Radio Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 18)
  - American Association of Textile Technology, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 19)
  - American Home Economics Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 20)
  - American Society of Ag Engineers, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 21)
  - American Society of Landscape Architecture, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 22)
  - American Society for Personnel Administration, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 23)
  - Association of Student Architects, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 24)
  - Armenian Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 25)
  - Asian American Coalition, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 26)
  - Astronomical Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 27)
  - Benvenuto Sanches Eating Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 28)
  - Bible Research, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 29)
  - Big Red in Blue, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 30)
  - Big Red Marching Band, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 31)
  - Black Bio-Med and Technical Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 32)
  - Black Students United, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 33)
  - B'nai B'rith Hillel, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 34)
  - Bowling Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 35)
  - Bowling, Women, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Bridge Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 37)
  - CIVITAS, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 38)
  - CUSLAR, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 39)
  - Centerpiece, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 40)
  - Cheerleaders, Varsity, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 41)
  - Chinese Cultural Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 42)
  - Chinese Dance Co., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 43)
  - Chinese Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 44)
  - Collegiate Future Farmers of America, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 45)
  - Combined Training Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 46)
  - Community against Sexism, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 47)
  - Community Dispute Resolution Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 48)
  - Conservatives at Cornell, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 49)
  - Cuban Cultural and Historical Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 50)
  - Cuban Studies Journal, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 51)
  - Cycling Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 52)
  - Dairy Science Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 53)
  - Debate Association - On Topic, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 54)
  - Debate - Parliamentary, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 55)
  - Delta Sigma Theta, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 56)
  - Diaspora Dance Theatre, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 57)
  - Dramatic Club Cornell, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 58)
  - Empathy, Assistance and Referral Service, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 59)
  - Economics Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 60)
  - Emergency Medical Service, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 61)
  - Engineer - Cornell, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 62)
  - Equestrian Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 63)
  - Ethos, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 64)
  - Fencers Club - Cornell, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 65)
  - Friends of Community Self-Reliance Center, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 66)
  - Gaelic Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 67)
  - GayPac, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 68)
  - Higher and Lower Tuition (H.A.L.T), 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 69)
  - Haitian Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 70)
  - Health's A Hoppin, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 71)
  - Hellenic Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 72)
  - Hong Kong Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 73)
  - Horseman's Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 74)
  - Hortus Forum, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 75)
  - Human Ecology Exchange, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 76)
  - IFC, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 77)
  - Independent Film Makers at Cornell, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 78)
  - International Students Programming Board, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 79)
  - Il Ciculo Italiano, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 80)
  - International Film Club of the I.L.C., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 81)
  - International Relations Seminar, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 82)
  - Internship Program, Cornell, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 83)
  - Israeli Folkdance, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 84)
  - Ithaca, Friends of Israel, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 85)
  - Ithaca Green Light Project, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 86)
  - Ithaca Rape Crisis, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 87)
  - Ithaca Women's Resource Center, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 88)
  - Japanese Cultural Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 89)
  - Cornell Jazz Ensemble, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 90)
  - Jordani Natural History Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 91)
  - Judo Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 92)
  - Kolenu-Jewish Student Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 93)
  - Korean Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 94)
  - La Association Latina, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 95)
  - Lesbian/Gay Pol. Action/Disc. Group, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 96)
  - Livestock Show, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 97)
  - Lunatic - Humor Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 98)
  - Makhela Hillel Choir, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 99)
  - Malaysian Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 100)
  - Minority Undergrad. Law Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 101)
  - Mexican American Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 102)
  - Minority Undergrad. Vets, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 103)
  - NCAA Volunteers for Youth, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 104)
  - Cornell Chapter of New York Civil Liberties Union, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 105)
  - National Society of Black Engineers, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 106)
  - North American Indians at Cornell, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 107)
  - Notables, The, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 108)
  - Outing Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 109)
  - Public Interest Research Group, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 110)
  - Pamoja-Ni Gospel Choir, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 111)
  - Pandacmonium Germanicum, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 112)
  - Parachute Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 113)
  - Peace Council, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 114)
  - Personal Growth Workshops, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 115)
  - Praxis, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 116)
  - Prison Project, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 117)
  - Progressive Zionist Alliance, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 118)
  - Quodlibet, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 119)
  - R/C Car Club of America, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 120)
  - Rainy-Day Literary Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 121)
  - Rifle Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 122)
  - Risley Residential, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 123)
  - Round-Up Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 124)